{
    "id": "c0d15a755a974ee28880104dbe38d219",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………… standing at the gate, I saw something strange.",
            "description": "While can be used to talk about two simultaneous actions or situations. ",
            "answers": [
                "While",
                "As",
                "When"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I know a shop ……………………….. they repair old watches.",
            "description": "Where means at which.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "there",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the park …………………………. we used to meet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ………………………… mother was seriously ill urged the doctors to save her life.",
            "description": "The relative pronoun whose indicates possession. ",
            "answers": [
                "whose",
                "who's",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… it was an old town, we couldn’t find any good accommodation.",
            "description": "As gives the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………………….. old to walk without support.",
            "description": "Note the patterns too...to...",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… her good performance, she was denied promotion.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition use it before a noun or noun phrase. ",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. she is very old, she is still very much on her own.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "Even if"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. did she get the message, than she started for home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "No sooner",
                "As soon as",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… he was the most deserving candidate, he had no difficulty getting the job.",
            "description": "As gives the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Though",
                "For"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You can stay with me ……………………………….. you take care of your expenses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "provided that",
                "so long as",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked a question ............................ no one could answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}